Tom Raymond Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series II: Photographs of Storyteller Performances
  - Color slides
    - Sea Island Singers (Georgia Sea Island Singers), GSIS:PH1-PH63 (Box-folder 7/118)
      Sea Island Singers, onstage and performing at the Swappin’ Ground. 63 35mm color slides.
    - Seeger, Pete, PPS:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 7/119)
      Publicity photographs of Pete Seeger. 2 35mm color slides.
    - Simms, Laura, LS:PH1-PH144 (Box-folder 7/120)
      Laura Simms onstage interacting with the audience and in candid shots on the grounds. 144 35mm color slides.
    - Smith, Jimmy Neil, JNS:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 7/121)
      Portraits photographs of Jimmy Neil Smith. 19 35mm color slides.
    - Smith, Mary Carter, MCS:PH1-PH40 (Box-folder 7/122)
      Mary Carter Smith performing in the gazebo at Ghost Stories and in candid shots on the grounds. 40 35mm color slides.
    - Spelman, Jon, JS:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 7/123)
      Jon Spelman performing offstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 2 35mm color slides.
    - Stivender, Ed (1/4), ES:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 7/124)
      Ed Stivender performing onstage and offstage on the grounds, also performing at the Fringe Festival in downtown Jonesborough and signing autographs. 200 35mm slides: 164 color and 36 black and white slides.
    - Stivender, Ed (2/4), ES:PH201-400 (Box-folder 7/125)
    - Stivender, Ed (3/4), ES:PH401-PH600 (Box-folder 8/126)
      Ed Stivender performing at the Fringe Festival and in candid shots on the grounds. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Stivender, Ed (4/4), ES:PH601-PH613 (Box-folder 8/127)
      13 35mm color slides.
    - Storycrafters (Barry Marshall and Jeri Burns), SC:PH1-PH25 (Box-folder 8/128)
      Storycrafters onstage. 25 35mm color slides.
    - Storyweavers (Lucinda Flodin, Dennis Frederick), SW:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 8/129)
      Storyweavers onstage. 19 35mm color slides.
    - Taifa, TA:PH1-PH85 (Box-folder 8/130)
      Taifa onstage. 85 35mm color slides.
    - Taylor, Rangimoana, RT:PH1-PH45 (Box-folder 8/131)
      Rangimoana Taylor onstage. 45 35mm color slides.
    - Teare, Billy, BT:PH1-PH16 (Box-folder 8/132)
      Billy Teare onstage. 16 35mm color slides.
    - Thomas, Taffy, TT:PH1-PH17 (Box-folder 8/133)
      Taffy Thomas onstage. 17 35mm color slides.
    - Thomason, Dovie, DT:PH1-PH16 (Box-folder 8/134)
      Dovie Thomason onstage. 16 35mm color slides.
    - Timpanelli, Gloria, GT:PH1-PH22 (Box-folder 8/135)
      Gloria Timpanelli onstage. 22 35mm color slides.
    - Torrence, Jackie (1/3), JT:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 8/136)
      Jackie Torrence onstage, interacting with the crowd and signing autographs and in candid shots on the ground. 200 35mm color slides.
    - Torrence, Jackie (2/3), JT:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 8/137)
    - Torrence, Jackie (3/3), JT:PH401-PH441 (Box-folder 8/138)
      Jackie Torrence onstage and in candid shots on the grounds. 40 35mm color slides.
    - Watkins, Kel, AKW:PH1-PH24 (Box-folder 8/139)
      Kel Watkins displaying images of string games. 24 35mm color slides.
    - Weakley, Tom, TW:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 8/140)
      Tom Weakley onstage. 12 35mm color slides.
    - Weir, Liz, LW:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 8/141)
      Liz Weir onstage, interacting with other storytellers and performing at the Fringe Festival. 12 35mm color slides.
    - Williams, Michael, MW:PH1 (Box-folder 8/142)
      Michael Williams in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slides.
    - Wilson, Madafo Lloyd, LW:PH1-PH42 (Box-folder 8/143)
      Lloyd Wilson performing at Swappin’ Ground. 42 35mm color slides.
    - Windham, Katherine, KTW:PH1-PH118 (Box-folder 8/144)
      Katherine Windham onstage and interacting with the crowd. 118 35mm color slides.
    - Wolkstein, Diane, DW:PH1 (Box-folder 8/145)
      Diane Wolkstein in candid shot on the grounds. 1 35mm color slide
    - Young, Judy Dockrey, JDY:PH1-PH93 (Box-folder 9/146)
      Judy Young performing on the lawn of Christopher Taylor Log Cabin. 93 35mm color slides.
    - Young, Yvonne, YY:PH1-PH45 (Box-folder 9/147)
      Yvonne Young performing at Swappin' Ground. 45 35mm color slides.
    - Zarzyski, Paul, PZ:PH1-PH38 (Box-folder 9/148)
      Paul Zarzyski onstage. 38 35mm color slides.
    - Unidentified Storytellers, US:PH1-PH27 (Box-folder 9/149)
      27 35mm color slides.
  - Color Reversal Film And Negatives
    - Adams, Sheila Kay, SKA:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/150)
      Sheila Kay Adams onstage at the Library Tent, 2004. 3 panoramic color negative strips.
    - Aoki, Brenda Wong, BWA:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 10/151)
      Brenda Wong Aoki onstage and publicity photographs. 5 35mm negatives strips and 9 60mm color reversal film.
    - Birch, Carol, CB:PH1-PH14 (Box-folder 10/152)
      Carol Birch onstage. 5 35mm color negative strips.
    - Black, Judith, Buck Ramsey and Joyce Grear, JB:PH1-PH37 (Box-folder 10/153)
      Judith Black, Buck Ramsey and Joyce Grear onstage. 13 35mm color negative strips.
    - Bragg, Bernard, BEB:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 10/154)
      Bernard Bragg portrait photographs. 2 matted 60mm color reversal films.
    - Burch, Mildred, MB:PH1-PH17 (Box-folder 10/155)
      Mildred Burch onstage, 1994. 6 35mm color negative strips.
    - Cabral, Len, LC:PH1 (Box-folder 10/156)
      Len Cabral publicity photograph. 1 60mm color reversal film (matted).
    - Clafin, Willy, CW:PH1-PH06 (Box-folder 10/157)
      Willy Clafin onstage at the College Street Tent, 2004. 3 panoramic negative film strips.
    - Davis, Donald, DD:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 10/158)
      Donald Davis onstage at the Theater Tent, 2004. 9 panoramic negative strips
    - Davis, Donald, DD:PH19-PH24 (Box-folder 10/158)
      Donald Davis and Tim Tingle onstage at the College Street and Library Tent. 6 panoramic negatives strips.
    - Davis, Donald, DD:PH25-PH31 (Box-folder 10/158)
      Donald Davis onstage. 7 60mm color reversal film.
    - Davis, Donald, DD:PH32-PH33 (Box-folder 10/158)
      2 35mm color reversal film (matted).
    - Dockery, Judy, JDY:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 10/159)
      Judy Dockery performing at Swappin’ Ground. 10 60mm color reversal film.
    - Ellis Elizabeth, 1943, and Ross, Gayle, EEGR:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/160)
      Elizabeth Ellis onstage. 6 35mm color reversal film (matted).
    - Ellis, Rex and Jay O’Callahan, RE:PH1-PH4 (Box-folder 10/161)
      Rex Ellis and Jay O'Callahan onstage. 4 35mm color reversal film (matted).
    - Ellis, Rex and Jay O’Callahan, JO:PH5-PH10 (Box-folder 10/161)
      Rex Ellis and Jay O'Callahan onstage at the College Street Tent. 3 panoramic negative strips.
    - Eth-Noh-Tech, ENT:PH1 (Box-folder 10/162)
      Eth-Noh-Tech onstage. 1 matted 35mm color reversal.
    - Eth-Noh-Tech, ENT:PH2-PH17 (Box-folder 10/162)
      Eth-Noh-Tech onstage, 1995. 6 35mm color negative strips
    - Jones, Francis Firebrace, FF:PH1-PH47 (Box-folder 10/163)
      Francis Firebrace Jones onstage. 47 60mm color reversal film.
    - Gillman, Jackson, JG:PH1 (Box-folder 10/164)
      Jackson Gillman onstage. 1 matted 35mm color reversal film.
    - Harley, Bill, BH:PH1 (Box-folder 10/165)
      Bill Harley publicity photograph. 1 60mm color reversal film.
    - Hicks, Ray, 1922-2003, RH:PH1-PH81 (Box-folder 10/166)
      Ray Hicks onstage, offstage and interacting with the crowd. 81 color reversal film: 14 35mm and 67 60mm (matted and unmatted).
    - Holloway, Martha, MH:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 10/167)
      Martha Halloway performing offstage. 20 60mm color reversal film (5 matted).
    - Holt, David, DH:PH1-PH7 (Box-folder 10/168)
      David Holt onstage. 7 35mm color negatives.
    - Jenkins, Robert, Bob, RJ:PH1-PH11 (Box-folder 10/169)
      Bob Jenkins onstage. 11 35mm color negatives.
    - Keams, Geri, GK:PH1 (Box-folder 10/170)
      Geri Keams onstage. 1 35mm negative.
    - Ledbetter, Gwenda, GL:PH1 (Box-folder 10/171)
      Gwenda Ledbetter onstage. 1 35mm color negative.
    - Lieberman, Syd, SL:PH1 (Box-folder 10/172)
      Syd Lieberman onstage. 1 35mm color negative.
    - Locke, Kevin, KL:PH1-PH9 (Box-folder 10/173)
      Kevin Locke onstage. 9 35mm color reversal film, 7 negative strips, 1 panoramic negative strip.
    - Lwanga, Namu, NL:PH1 (Box-folder 10/174)
      Namu Lwanga onstage. 1 35mm color negative.
    - McCutcheon, John, JMC:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 10/175)
      John McCutcheon onstage. 12 60mm color reversal film.
    - McBride-Smith, Barbara, BMS:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 10/176)
      Barbara McBride-Smith onstage. 3 35mm color negatives.
    - McConnell, Doc, DM:PH1-PH8 (Box-folder 10/177)
      Doc McConnell performing his "Old Medicine Show" on the grounds at Christopher Log Cabin, 1992. 8 color reversal film (Panoramic).
    - McConnell, Doc, DM:PH:9-PH18 (Box-folder 10/177)
      Doc McConnell performing his "Old Medicine Show" in the court yard, International Storytelling Center. 10 60mm color reversal film
    - McConnell, Doc, DM:PH19 (Box-folder 10/177)
      Doc McConnell onstage, 1995. 1 matted 35mm negative.
    - Mitchell, Waddie, 1950 and Don Edwards, WMDE:PH1-PH36 (Box-folder 10/178)
      Waddie Mitchell and Don Edwards onstage. 9 35mm negative strips reversal film.
    - Mooney William, BM:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 10/179)
      Bill Mooney onstage. 6 panoramic negative film.
    - Moses, Johnny and Martha Holloway, JM:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 10/180)
      Johnny Moses onstage. 3 60mm color reversal film and 2 35mm color negatives (matted).
    - Moses, Johnny and Martha Holloway, JM:PH6-PH11 (Box-folder 10/180)
      Johnny Moses along with Martha Holloway onstage, 1995. 6 35mm negative strips.
    - Norfolk, Bobby, BN:PH1-PH31 (Box-folder 10/181)
      Bobby Norfolk offstage on the grounds. 31 60mm color reversal film; (4 matted)
    - O’Callahan, Jay, JO: PH1-PH9 (Box-folder 10/182)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage. 9 35 mm color negatives (matted).
    - O’Callahan, Jay, JO:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 10/182)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage. 2 panoramic color reversal film.
    - O’Callahan, Jay, Hannah O’Callahan and Tim Tingle, JOJT:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/183)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage at the Theater Festival Tent, 2004. 3 panoramic negative film.
    - O’Callahan, Jay, Hannah O’Callahan and Tim Tingle, JOJT:PH7-PH12 (Box-folder 10/183)
      Jay O’Callahan and his daughter performing inside the College Street Tent at the 2004, International Storytelling Festival in Jonesborough, Tennessee. 3 panoramic negative film.
    - O’Callahan, Jay, Hannah O’Callahan and Tim Tingle, JOJT:PH13-PH18 (Box-folder 10/183)
      Jay O’Callahan and Tim Tingle performing inside the Theater Festival Tent at the 2004, International Storytelling Festival in Jonesborough, Tennessee. 3 panoramic negative film.
    - O’Callahan, Jay, Hannah O’Callahan and Tim Tingle, JOJT:PH19 (Box-folder 10/183)
      Jay O’Callahan onstage. 1 panoramic negative.
    - Parker “Mac” Michael and Brummett, Curt, MMP:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 10/184)
      Mac Parker onstage, 1994. 2 35mm color negative strips.
    - Parker “Mac” Michael and Brummett, Curt, CB:PH6-PH9 (Box-folder 10/184)
      Curt Brummitt onstage, 1994. 2 35mm color reversal film
    - Rauch, Debbie, DR:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 10/185)
      Debbie Rauch onstage. 10 60mm color reversal film.
    - Regan-Blake, Connie, 1947 and Barbara Freeman, CR-BBF:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/186)
      Connie Regan-Blake and Barbara Freeman onstage. 6 60mm color reversal film.
    - Raynor-Pershin, Laura, LPR:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/187)
      Laura Pershin-Raynor onstage. 3 panoramic negative film strips.
    - Reneaux, J.J., JJR:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 10/188)
      J. J. Reneaux onstage. 2 35mm color negatives (matted).
    - Rocha, Antonio, AR:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 10/189)
      Antonio Rocha onstage at the Theater Festival Tent, 2004. 6 panoramic negative film strips.
    - Rocha, Antonio, AR:PH13-PH22 (Box-folder 10/189)
      Antonio Rocha onstage. 12 60mm negatives
    - Rogers, Gamble, GR:PH1-PH35 (Box-folder 10/190)
      Gamble Rogers onstage. 35 60mm color reversal film.
    - Rogers, Gamble, GR:PH36-PH59 (Box-folder 10/190)
      Gamble Rogers and M. Williams onstage, 1988. 24 60mm color reversal film
    - SCALA, SC:PH1-PH54 (Box-folder 10/191)
      Various storytellers onstage and offstage on the grounds. 54 60mm color reversal film.
    - Seeger Pete, PS:PH1-PH2: (Box-folder 10/192)
      Pete Seeger publicity photographs. 2 60mm color reversal film.
    - Smith, Jimmy Neil, JNS:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/193)
      Jimmy Neil Smith portrait photographs. 6 60mm color reversal film; 2 matted.
    - Stivender, Ed, ES:PH1-PH22 (Box-folder 10/194)
      Ed Stivender onstage. 22 60mm color reversal film.
    - Stivender, Ed, ES:PH23 (Box-folder 10/194)
      Ed Stivender onstage. 1 60mm color reversal film
    - Tinh (Mahoney, Tinh), TI:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/195)
      Tinh onstage at the Creekside Festival Tent, 2004. 3 panoramic negative strips.
    - Torrence, Jackie, JT:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 10/196)
      Jackie Torrence onstage. 17 60mm color reversal film and 5 35mm color negatives.
    - Torrence, Jackie, JT:PH6-PH9 (Box-folder 10/196)
      Jackie Torrence onstage, 1992. 4 56 x 112 mm color reversal
    - Washington, Donna, DW:PH1-PH6: (Box-folder 10/197)
      Donna Washington onstage. 3 panoramic negative strips.
    - Zarzyski, Paul, PZ:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 10/198)
      Paul Zarzyski onstage. 2 35mm color negatives.
- Series III: Photographs of Various Storytellers
  - Color Reversal Film And Negatives
    - Various Storytellers (1/12), VS:PH1-PH53 (Box-folder 11/199)
      53 60mm black and white negative film.
    - Various Storytellers (2/12), VS:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 11/200)
      9 panoramic negative film and 10 60mm reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (3/12), VS:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 11/201)
      20 60mm reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (4/12), VS:PH1-PH3 (Box-folder 11/202)
      2 60mm color reversal film and 1 35mm color negative.
    - Various Storytellers (5/12), VS:PH1-PH43 (Box-folder 11/203)
      43 60mm color reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (6/12), VS:PH1-PH7 (Box-folder 11/204)
      7 60mm color reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (7/12), VS:PH1-PH20 (Box-folder 11/205)
      20 56 x 112 mm color reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (8/12), VS:PH1-PH17 (Box-folder 11/206)
      17 strips 35mm color reversal film and 1 matted.
    - Various Storytellers (9/12), VS:PH1-PH87 (Box-folder 11/207)
      87 35mm color negative strips.
    - Various Storytellers (10/12), VS:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 11/208)
      19 35mm color negative strips.
    - Various Storytellers (11/12), VS:PH1-PH5 (Box-folder 11/209)
      5 60mm color reversal film.
    - Various Storytellers (12/12), VS:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 11/210)
      18 35mm color negative strips.
- Series IV: Photographs of Events
  - Color Slides
    - Children Storytelling, CS:PH1-PH64 (Box-folder 12/211)
      64 35mm color slides.
    - The Fringe Festival (1/3), TF:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 12/212)
      200 35mm slides: 180 color and 20 black and white.
    - The Fringe Festival (2/3), TF:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 12/213)
    - The Fringe Festival (3/3), TF: PH401-PH451 (Box-folder 12/214)
      51 35mm slides: 34 color and 17 black and white.
    - Ghost Stories (1/2), GS:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 12/215)
    - Ghost Stories (2/2), GS:PH201-PH254 (Box-folder 12/216)
      54 35mm color slides.
    - Native American Indians, NAI:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 12/217)
      6 35mm color slides.
    - International Storytelling Center, 2003, ISC:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 12/218)
      19 35mm color slides.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes (1/4), SC:PH1-PH200 (Box-folder 12/219)
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes (2/4), SC:PH201-PH400 (Box-folder 13/220)
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes (3/4), SC:PH401-600 (Box-folder 13/221)
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes (4/4), SC:PH601-PH657 (Box-folder 13/222)
      57 35mm color slides.
    - Swappin’ Ground, SG:PH1-PH72 (Box-folder 13/223)
      72 35mm color slides.
    - Swatches, SW:PH1-PH71 (Box-folder 13/224)
      71 35mm color slides.
  - Color Reversal Film And Negatives
    - Al Gore Event, 1995 (1/2), AGE:PH1-PH19 (Box-folder 14/225)
      Al Gore’s 1995 visit to the International Storytelling Festival. 19 black and white negative strips.
    - Al Gore Event, 1995 (2/2), AGE:PH1-PH40 (Box-folder 14/226)
      Al Gore’s 1995 visit to the International Storytelling Festival, along with images of Ray Hicks. 40 35mm negative strips.
    - Doc McConnell’s Old Time Medicine Show, DMO:PH1-PH30 (Box-folder 14/227)
      30 panoramic film.
    - The Fringe Festival (1/2), FF:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 14/228)
      6 35mm color negative strips.
    - The Fringe Festival (2/2), FF:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 14/229)
      9 color reversal film, 7 60mm color reversal film, 1 35mm color negative and 1 panoramic film.
    - Ghost Stories (1/2), GH:PH1-PH104 (Box-folder 14/230)
      104 color reversal film: 20 matted; 84 60mm, 38 panoramic and 1 35mm negative.
    - Ghost Stories (2/2), GH:PH1-PH13 (Box-folder 14/231)
      13 35mm color negative strips.
    - Hicks, Ray (Funeral Service), RHF:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 14/232)
      18 60mm negative film.
    - Hicks, Ray (Beech Mountain, N.C.), RHB:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 14/233)
      10 panoramic color reversal film.
    - International Storytelling Center, Yarnspinner Party, October 1994, YP94:PH1-PH9 (Box-folder 14/234)
      9 60mm color reversal film.
    - International Storytelling Center, Yarnspinner Party, October, 1995, YP95:PH1-PH17 (Box-folder 14/235)
      17 60mm color reversal film.
    - International Storytelling Center, Open House, OH:PH1-PH9 (Box-folder 14/236)
      9 35mm black and white negative strips.
    - Kripsy Kreme, KK:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 14/237)
      18 panoramic negatives.
    - Resource Tent, 1995, RT95:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 14/238)
      6 35mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling crowds, (1/2), SC:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 14/239)
      12 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling crowds, (2/2), SC:PH13-PH48 (Box-folder 14/240)
      36 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, 1994, SCS94:PH1-PH28 (Box-folder 14/241)
      28 color reversal film: 15 60mm color reversal film and 13 panoramic film.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, 2001, SCS01:PH1-PH30 (Box-folder 14/242)
      30 60mm negatives.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, (1/3), SCS1:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 14/243)
      Crowds attending the International Storytelling Festival and Main St. Jonesborough, Tennessee. 12 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, (2/3), SCS2:PH3-PH24 (Box-folder 14/244)
      Ariel and ground view of Main Street Jonesborough, Tennessee. 12 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, Jonesborough, Tennessee (3/3), SCS3:PH25-PH28 (Box-folder 14/245)
      Scenes in Jonesborough, Tennessee. 4 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling festival tents, street and scenes(1/4), STS1:PH1-PH7 (Box-folder 14/246)
      7 60mm color reversal film and 1 35mm negative.
    - Storytelling festival tents, street and scenes (2/4), STS2:PH8-PH17 (Box-folder 14/247)
      Showcases the different Railroad, Creekside, College Street, Library tents and more. 105 color film: 10 60mm color reversal film and 95 panoramic film.
    - Storytelling festival tents, street and scenes (3/4), STS3:PH18-PH89 (Box-folder 14/248)
      72 panoramic film.
    - Storytelling crowds and street scenes, Storytelling tents (4/4), STS4:PH90-PH93 (Box-folder 14/249)
      64 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling festival tents, Tent In The Park, TN:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 14/250)
      10 35mm color negative strips.
    - Storytelling festival tents, Various (1/3), STV1:PH1-PH10 (Box-folder 14/251)
      10 60mm color reversal film.
    - Storytelling festival tents, Various (2/3), STV2:PH11-PH28 (Box-folder 14/252)
      18 panoramic black and white film.
    - Storytelling festival tents, Various (3/3), STV3:PH29-PH67 (Box-folder 14/253)
      39 60mm black and white film.
    - Swappin’ Ground, 1995, SG95:PH1-PH27 (Box-folder 14/254)
      27 60mm color reversal film.
  - Photographic prints
    - Biltmore Estate (Event), BE:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 15/255)
      Architectural photograph. 2 8x10 black-and-white print.
    - Midnight Cabaret, 1997 (Event), MC97:PH1-PH37 (Box-folder 15/256)
      Waddie Mitchell and Don Edwards onstage at the Midnight Cabaret, 1997. 37 4x6 color prints.
    - Mujuru, Ephat, EM:PH1-PH3 (Box-folder 15/257)
      Ephat Mujuru onstage. 2 5x7 and 1 8x10 black-and-white prints.
    - O’Callahan, Jay, JO:PH1-PH3 (Box-folder 15/258)
      Jay O'Callahan performing in front of Doc McConnell’s wagon. 3 5x7 black and white prints.
    - Ross, Gayle, GR:PH1 (Box-folder 15/259)
      Gayle Ross, onstage. 1 8x10 black and white.
    - Rubright, Lynn, LR:PH1-PH8 (Box-folder 15/260)
      Lynn Rubright onstage. 8 5x7 black and white prints.
    - Storytelling exhibit, SE:PH1-PH12 (Box-folder 15/261)
      Various storytellers onstage and offstage on the grounds. 11 8x10 and 1 5x7 black and white prints.
    - Swappin' Ground, SW:PH1-PH3 (Box-folder 15/262)
      Ray Hicks and Storytelling audience at the Swappin' Ground. 2 8x10 and 1 5x7 black and white prints.
    - Timpanelli, Goya, GT:PH1 (Box-folder 15/263)
      Goya Timpanelli onstage. 1 5x7 black and white print.
    - Various Storytellers (1/2), VS1:PH1-PH18 (Box-folder 15/264)
      Various storytellers onstage and offstage on the grounds along with interacting with audience. 14 black and white prints: 4 5x7 and 10 8x10.
    - Various Storytellers (2/2), VS2:PH19-PH32 (Box-folder 15/265)
      14 8x10 black and white prints.
    - Young, Judy, JY:PH1-PH4 (Box-folder 15/266)
      Judy Young onstage. 4 8x10 black and white print.
  - Contact Sheets
    - Hicks, Ray, RH:PH1-PH2 (Box-folder 15/267)
      Contact sheets which also includes Jackie Torrence. 2 black and white contact sheets.
    - Krispy Kreme, KK:PH1-PH3 (Box-folder 15/268)
      Contact sheets displaying the Krispy Donuts trailer in the town of Jonesbourough, Tennessee. 3 contact sheets.
    - NAPPS staff and storytellers, 1984, NS84:PH1-PH4 (Box-folder 15/269)
      Contacts sheets of NAPPS staff, now ISC, and Storytellers attending an event and performing. 4 contact sheets.
    - International National Storytelling Festival, NSF:PH1-PH22 (Box-folder 15/270)
      Scenes from the International National Storytelling Festival. 22 color prints (various sizes).
    - Various Storytellers (1/3), VS1:PH1-PH6 (Box-folder 15/271)
      Contact sheets of various storytellers such as David Holt, Ed Stivender and more onstage. 6 color contact sheets.
    - Various Storytellers (2/3), VS2:PH7-PH10 (Box-folder 15/272)
      Contact Sheets of various storytellers onstage. 4 color contact sheets.
    - Various Storytellers (3/3), VS3:PH11-PH23 (Box-folder 15/273)
      Contact sheets of various storytellers including Doc Mc Connell’s "Old Medicine Show." 13 color contact sheets.